Speaker 1: I've been in a few fights in my day.
Speaker 1: About two hundo, maybe two fitty.
Speaker 1: Yeah!
Speaker 1: You're dead, Becky!
Speaker 1: Where did the time go?
Speaker 1: Roger, just have a look around.
Speaker 1: There are plenty of other fish in the sea.
Speaker 3: I know you're proud of yourself for coming up with that, but I just want Klaus back.
Speaker 1: Well, when you love someone, you have to go after them.
Speaker 3: Is that how you got Stan?
Speaker 1: Bitch, I look like this.
Speaker 1: Homegirl don't chase.
Speaker 3: Homegirl gets chased.
Speaker 3: Klaus wanted taboo.
Speaker 3: And danger.
Speaker 3: I can give that to him.
Speaker 3: I'm gonna make this work!
Speaker 1: Homegirl don't even have to work!
Speaker 1: Homegirl get that paper all on her own!
Speaker 3: Stop that.
Speaker 3: You're white.
Speaker 1: I'm Homegirl.
Speaker 4: Thanks for letting me go back on my medication, Mrs.
Speaker 4: S.
Speaker 1: Better than the alternative.
Speaker 1: Stan, from now on, I'll be taking all of Steve's spankings on his behalf.
Speaker 1: What?
Speaker 1: Why?
Speaker 1: Because his mistakes are a reflection on my parenting.
Speaker 1: When Steve fails, I fail.
Speaker 0: I don't know if that sounds... And he kept calling fouls like a bitch!
Speaker 0: Oh, well, I am gonna punish you on his behalf for that.
Speaker 5: Mama, the man said someone died upstairs.
Speaker 5: What if I see a g-g-ghost?
Speaker 0: I don't know, Steve.
Speaker 1: You'll probably p-p-p-p-p-pitch your pants.
Speaker 1: Where am I?
Speaker 1: A hotel room.
Speaker 1: You're getting a lot better at drinking, Francine.
Speaker 2: Francine, I think I figured out why your catchphrase fell flat.
Speaker 1: Because it was a stupid idea.
Speaker 2: No, the words are right, just not the delivery.
Speaker 2: Try saying it like you've just been on a road trip through the South.
Speaker 1: Things are getting too spicy for the pepper!
Speaker 2: Now more like you just came in from playing in the snow, but you haven't had your hot chocolate yet.
Speaker 2: Things are getting too spicy for the pepper!
Speaker 2: Maybe more a mix of sadness that your dog died, relief because he was riddled with fatty lymphomas, and joy that you can now get a new kitty!
Speaker 1: Things are getting too spicy for the pepper!
Speaker 2: Watch Oscar-nominated actress Gabourey Sidibe do it.
Speaker 3: Things are getting too spicy for the pepper.
Speaker 0: Francine, are you sure about this?
Speaker 1: Look, the sooner we kill this guy, the sooner we can start enjoying ourselves.
Speaker 1: Oh, I signed us up for hot air ballooning at sunset?
Speaker 0: Think we'll nail this guy by then?
Speaker 0: I-I'm not sure.
Speaker 1: Come on, what's so hard about it?
Speaker 1: Bam, bam, bam!
Speaker 1: I just killed that waiter, a baby, and a fat guy on a rascal.
Speaker 0: But honey, Joe is the outdoor activities director.
Speaker 0: He's always surrounded by people.
Speaker 0: So kill them all!
Speaker 0: I think it's hot when you talk like that, but that's not how we do things at the CIA.
Speaker 0: Look, I just need you to get him alone, then I can shoot him.
Speaker 1: Okay, well, you figure it out while I take out these two.
Speaker 1: Should have done that a long time ago.
Speaker 2: About time.
Speaker 0: It's 4 o'clock.
Speaker 3: Where are my 4 o'clock nachos?
Speaker 1: I got this one.
Speaker 1: Steven Smith, I am your mother!
Speaker 1: If you don't get out of that cage, I will push you back up my clown hole and birth you again and name you my bitch!
Speaker 1: Now get out of that cage!
Speaker 1: Let me out of here!
Speaker 1: I'll let you out when Steve's a national champion.
Speaker 1: Here's a Nintendo to keep you busy.
Speaker 1: My mother says video games are bad for you.
Speaker 1: Yeah, well, so is smoking an eight ball of crack in 30 minutes, but that's how long it takes.
Speaker 1: What's up, Mountain Douche?
Speaker 1: Want a pound of cold one?
Speaker 0: Um, what?
Speaker 0: I was thinking we were going to have dinner.
Speaker 0: Why is there a ping pong table in here?
Speaker 1: Uh, so we can play beer pong?
Speaker 0: I don't understand what's going on here.
Speaker 0: What's going on here is shots!
Speaker 0: Shots!
Speaker 0: So what time is dinner gonna be?
Speaker 1: Six.
Speaker 0: Nemo turned Steve into an apostate of Satan!
Speaker 1: He's probably just hungry.
Speaker 1: Steve, I just did a big Trader Joe's run.
Speaker 1: Pour yourself some unsweetened cherry juice, maybe have it with some sunflower paste on a flax crisp.
Speaker 1: There's also a scallop shumai that tastes like nothing and a mushroom flatbread pizza that smells like nut sack.